如果你需要上厕所  只要出门直走就可以
And if you need the restroom, it's just back that way.
得了吧
Nah.
在我进来之前就在你们走廊上留了领地标记了
Marked my territory on your porch before I came in.
噢  身上好痒
Ooh, got an itch.
挠不到  挠不到
Can't get it. Can't get it.
- 挠不到  - 好吧
- Can't get it. - Okay.
帮帮同类啊
Help a wolf out!
噢
Oh!
啊  这就舒服多了
Ahh, that's the stuff.
是吗
Yeah?
这狼孩简直疯了
Wolf girl is cray cray.
不过我还需要她训练我身上那种丛林山野的气息
But she is going to give me the forest cred
我才能通过这次试镜
that I need to really nail this audition.
有本事你就把那从马路上拖下来吃了啊  戈斯林
Scrape that off the road and eat it, Gosling.
这些是从把我养大的狼家里带出来的东西
This is from the forest where my wolf family raised me.
这些东西的的味道都不太好闻
Lots of good stink to roll around in.
哦
Oh!
啊
Ah.
舒服啊
Ahh.
到你了  小狼崽子
Your turn, wolf pup.
去打打滚吧
Get up in it.
好吧
Okay.
呼
Whoo.
看看我
Look at me.
在一堆脏兮兮的东西上蹭来蹭去
Scooting around in the filth.
呼
Whoo.
就像是动物一样
Like an animal.
我真是野性十足啊
I am wild!
- 鲁尼  - 怎么了
- Rooney... - Yeah?
- 我就把话直说了吧  - 嗯哼
- Can I get real for a minute? - Mm-hmm?
如果你想在试镜中脱颖而出  你就要像真狼一样
If you want to ace this audition, you have to go full wolf.
狼是领地意识很强的动物
Wolves are territorial animals.
- 好的  - 它们拿走了的东西
- Yeah. - They take what's theirs,
- 就永远别想拿回来了  - 好吧
- and they don't back down. - Yeah.
我们来试试别的吧
Let's try something else.
干嘛呢
What?
你想拿回去么
You want it?
来抢啊
Take it.
好吧
Okay.
我这就去拿水枪
I'm gonna go get the hose.